

Rawezh Dilshad Noori

CONTACT

E-mail: rdmentalist@gmail.com,

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/jrdm/

Phone: 009647717115267 009647701096332

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality: Iraqi

Date Of Birth: 08/11/1992 Place Of Birth: Kirkuk, Iraq a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry, Experience with Samsung & Apple authorized stores as showrooms manager, stock keeper, system logistics and maintenance supervisor.

Experienced Smartphone Maintenance Engineer. Skilled in AutoCAD, Maintenance, Microsoft Excel, Technical Support and Computer Softwares, Using Photo and Video editors on regular basis.

Fluent in English & Arabic, Can work in Erbil & Sulaymaniyah

EDUCATION

College of Engineering

Kirkuk University

Bachelor's Degree in Mechanical Engineering (2014-2015)

Honors and Rewards

Best Graduation Project – 2015 Engineering Fair

Design and Build of Automated Robotic Arm controlled by PC and motion sensor.

Apple Services Certifications

- Apple Service Fundamentals / ACiT 2019 iOS Service / ACMT 2019 Mac Service

SKILLS

- Web design and very good with researching and collecting information.
- Very good with computers and Programing (Matlab, visual Basic, solid works and AutoCAD)
- Microsoft Word and Excel (Used on a daily basis)
- Very good, fast in typing
- Precise translation skills (orally or formal letters)
- Body language Observation, Persuasion techniques and Good communication
- Able to speak three languages:

English (Native or Bilingual)

Arabic (Full Professional)

Kurdish (Native or Bilingual)

1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Master Group

Showrooms Manager

Feb 2021 - November 2021 (Erbil)

- Studying the features of all products on offer and Arranging stock between Iraq showrooms.
- Maintains staff by recruiting, selecting, orienting and Training them in effective sales and communication strategies representing Apple.
- Documenting sales and Advising Purchasers on items that ought to be restocked or removed from the catalog.
- Ensuring that showroom Demo models are set up and in working condition.
- Evaluating the possibility of new suitable retail store locations across Iraq.

Apple Sales Support Specialist / Maintenance Services

December 2019 - Feb 2021 (Sulaymaniyah)

- Apple Showroom Sales Services:
- Help customers find items in the store.
- Check for stock at other branches or order requested stock for customers.
- Provide customers with information about items and help them choose the right device.
- Keep track of inventory.
 - Apple Technical Support:

Providing maintenance services for apple products when required and help customers with ios, macos related issues.

Freelance Software Engineer

March 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 7 months) Sulaymaniyah

> Self Employed and Photoshop Designer, Sales and Software maintenance and sales of different electronics devices such as (Consoles/Laptops)

<u> JiBAL Mobile</u>

Samsung Maintenance Engineer

April 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 11 months) Kirkuk, Sulaymaniyah - Iraq

- Samsung Smartphone Maintenance and Technical Support at Kirkuk SVC.
- Spare parts Stock management through the official GSPN System, and checking the warranty of Samsung smart phones.
- Troubleshooting any problems faced, whether they were system related or customer related.

*References will be provided upon request

SAMSUNG



No: 53

Date:30/04/2018

To\ Whom It may Concern Subject\ Reference Letter

Dear Sir/ Madam,

This is to confirm that Mr. RAWEJ DILSHAD NURI was working in our company from April 2016 until February 2018 as Samsung maintenance engineer & spare parts stock manager and during this time he did his work very accurate and success and was responsible for the whole Iraq.

For more information please feel free to contact us.

Saman Alaaddin General Manager

